McConnell, John W., Papers /3052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Misc. Stuff on Old Age and Retirement (Box 39, Folder 5)
- NYS Dept. of Labor - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 6)
- NY Clothing Manufacturers Exchange, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Retirement Misc. (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Correspondence. - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Aging and the Economy (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Aging (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Aged and Society: A Symposium on the Problems of an Aging Population (Review) (Box 40, Folder 3)
- America's Needs and Resources - Welfare (Box 40, Folder 4)
- America's Needs and Resources - Welfare [cont.] (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Aging - Reports & News Releases (Box 40, Folder 6)
- America's Needs and Resources - Welfare (Box 40, Folder 7)
- America's Needs and Resources - Welfare [cont.] (Box 40, Folder 8)
- America's Needs and Resources - Welfare = Institute, Personal, Family Allowances, Resources (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Book Reviews (Box 40, Folder 10)
- British Social Security 15 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- British Social Security System (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Case for Federal Relief (Sat. Eve. Post) (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Wilbur Cohen: Legislative Evolution of the Social Security Amendments of 1952 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Conference - Council of Churches - Buffalo (Box 40, Folder 15)
- COOP Pension & Retirement (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Disability Compensation - 11 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Disability Compensation - 11 [cont.] (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Disability Compensation - Workmen's Compensation Bd. (State of N.Y.) (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Economic Aspects of Benefit Programs by McConnell & W. Cohen (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Economic and Social Problems of Adjustment of Older Workers (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Economic Position of the Elderly (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Employee Adjustment to Technological Displacement - by McConnell & B. Lampert (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Employment Stabilization Private (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Employment Stabilization Private (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Employment Stabilization Public (Box 41, Folder 7)
- European Systems of Social Insurance (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Expend. For Community Health & Welfare, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Fringe Benefits - War Labor Board (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Guaranteed Annual Wage (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Guaranteed Annual Wage [cont.] (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Guaranteed Annual Wage (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Guaranteed Annual Wage [cont.] (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Health and Welfare (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Health and Welfare: Misc. Reports (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Health Benefits - Misc. Reports - Health Ins. (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Health Fund of the ILGWU (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Health Ins. (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Health Ins. (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Health Ins. - Private & Vol. Plans (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Herald -Tribune: June 15, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Hist. of the Soc. Sec. Leg. In the U.S. (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Human Relations (lecture in T-Burg) (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Human Relations in Industry (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Impact of Aging on the Economy (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Industrial Retirement (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Industrial Sociology (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Industry and the Older Worker (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Labor Relations & Human Relations (Review) (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Meeting University - Gov't. Center (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Nature and Types of Insecurity (Box 42, Folder 18)
- New Zealand Social Security (Box 42, Folder 19)
- New Zealand Social Security System (Box 42, Folder 20)
- OAA Recipients in Ithaca (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Old Age Research Proposal - Streib Suchman (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Old Age & Retirement (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Older Workers - Misc. Reports (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Older Worker in Industry (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Accidental Injuries - Henry H. Kessler (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Admin. Of Placement and Unempl. Ins. in Germany by Oscar Weigart (Box 43, Folder 2)
- After the Shutdown & Employee Adj. to Technological Displacement (Box 43, Folder 3)
- After Unemployment Benefits are Exhausted - Myers and MacLaurin (Box 43, Folder 4)
- America and the Beveridge Plan - E. Wight Bakke (Box 43, Folder 5)
- America and the Beveridge Plan - E. Wight Bakke (Box 43, Folder 6)
- An Analysis of "100 Hundred Neediest Cases" (Box 43, Folder 7)
- An Analysis of two Supreme Court Decisions Workmen's Comp. (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Benefits & Contributions (Box 43, Folder 9)
- British Unemployment Programs - 1920-1938 - Eveline Burns (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Challenge of the Aged - Abraham Epstein (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Characteristics of State Plans for Old-Age Assistance, Aid to the Blind, and Aid to Dependent Children (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Compensation for Unemployment During Industrial Dispute (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Complete Set Reports for ILR 107 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Compulsory Sickness Compensation for New York State (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Compulsory Sickness Compensation for New York State (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Conf. of Commission on Comp. for Industrial Accidents, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Data on Disqualifications Retirement Pay (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Disability Evaluation - Earl D. McBride (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Development of Public Welfare Services (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Developments in the social security program - J. Douglas Brown (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Dismissal Compensation - Everett D. Hawkins (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Dynamic Elements in a full empl. Program - Harvey S. Perloff (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Economic Aspects of Medical Services: With special Ref. to conditions in Calif. - Paul A. Dodd and E.F. Penrose (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Effects of H.-A. Bill Tax Rates (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Empire Livestock Marketing (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Evolution of Communist Policy Toward Social Security (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Experience Rating Operations in 1946 and 1947, 1946-1947 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Federal Role in Unempl. Comp. Admin. - by Raymond C. Atkinson (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Federal State Unemployment Ins. - Bryce Stewart (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Friendly Societies (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Full Empl. In your Community (Box 43, Folder 32)
- General Account (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Group Rate - Small Employers (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Guarantee of Work and Wages - Snider; Guarantee of Annual Wages - Kaplan; Annual Wage - Feldman (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Guaranteed Wage Plans in the U.S. - Bulletin 925 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Guaranteed Wages in the Year Round / Steel Fights for the Nation (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Hansen and Samuelson - Appendix to Latimer Report (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Health Bills in the 81st Congress 1st Session (Box 43, Folder 39)
- Health Ins. Doctor - Barbara N. Armstrong (Box 43, Folder 40)
- Hearings Before Comm. Of Educ. And Labor, U.S. Senate, 79th Congress (Box 43, Folder 41)
- Hearings on H.R. 4120, Comm. On Ways and Means, Jan. 21 to Feb. 12, 1935 (Box 43, Folder 42)
- History of Workmen's comp. Legislation in N.Y. State, 1910-1917 (Box 43, Folder 43)
- Hohaus Proposal and Related Material (Box 43, Folder 44)
- I.A.P.E.S. Conf. - NYC - May 2 (Box 43, Folder 45)
- Industrial Pensions by Charles L. Dearing (Box 43, Folder 46)
- Industry Studies (Box 43, Folder 47)
- Issues in U.I. (Box 43, Folder 48)
- Joint Legislative Conf. (Box 43, Folder 49)
- Latimer Report - Guaranteed Annual Wage (Box 43, Folder 50)
- Loysen Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 51)
- Medical Care for the American people (Box 43, Folder 52)
- Medical Care for the People of NYS (Box 43, Folder 53)
- Message Covering Fiscal Year 1956 (Box 43, Folder 54)
- Nations Health (Box 43, Folder 55)
- 1939 Amendments to the Social Security Act (Box 43, Folder 56)
- Old Age in New York City by Helen Brunot (Box 43, Folder 57)
- Old Age in Sweden - Helen Fisher Hohman (Box 43, Folder 58)
- Old Age Plans and Programs of Farmers (Box 43, Folder 59)
- Old Age Security - Social and Financial Trends - Margaret Grant (Box 43, Folder 60)
- Operation of Second Injury Funds (Box 43, Folder 61)
- Pillars of Security - William H. Beveridge (Box 43, Folder 62)
- Preface to Peasantry by Arthur Raper (Box 43, Folder 63)
- Private Group Retirement Plans by Birchard E.Wyatt (Box 43, Folder 64)
- Problems of Workmen's Compensation Admin. In U.S. and Canada by Marshall Dawson (Box 43, Folder 65)
- Program - 1957 (Box 43, Folder 66)
- Public Assistance - A report to the Senate Comm. On Finance from the Advisory Comm. On Social Security (Box 43, Folder 67)
- Public Employment Service in the United States - Atkinson, Odencrantz, Deming (Box 43, Folder 68)
- Public Medical Care - Frank Goldmann (Box 43, Folder 69)
- Railroad Retirement Acts and Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Recommendations for Social Security Legislation (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Report on the Functions of Reserves in Old-Age Benefit Plans by Karl Pribram (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Report on Unemployment Insurance, Doc. 208 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Report on Unemployment Insurance, Doc. 208 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Report to the Dean on Activities - 1954-55, 1954-1955 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Research Project (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Report to the Legislature of the State of New York by the Commission 1909 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Reserve provisions of the federal old-age security program by M. Albert Linton (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Retirement Seminar Requests (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Roosevelt and Hopkins - Robert E. Sherwood (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Seasonal Industries (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Senate Advisory Council on Social Security - Report on Old Age and Survivors Insurance (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Sickness Insurance (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Elements of Policy with Respect to Public Assistance in the U.S. (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Size of Fund (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Social Insurance and Allied Services - William Beveridge (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Social Insurance in Europe and Social Security in the United States: a comparative analysis (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Social Security in America (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Social Security in America: Social Security Board (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Social Security in the United States - Paul H. Douglas, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Social Security Act in Operation - Wyatt and Wandel (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Social Security Organization in the Federal Government (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Social Security Plans in Great Britain - Int'l. Labor Review (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Social Security System of the Modern Factory by Lloyd Warner and J.O. Law (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Statistics (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Statute Law Relating to Employment - F.N. Ball (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Summary of Beatrice Webb's Activities and Observations with the Royal Commission of the Poor Law (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Supplementary - U.I. (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Synopsis of Elizabethian Poor Law of 1601 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Taxes (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Taxable Payrolls (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Ten Years of Social Security (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Top Priority Mail (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Torch Club (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Towards Social Security - Eveline Burns (Box 44, Folder 36)
- 2 Year Qualifying Period (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Unemployment - Labor Force - NY Industries (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Unemployment - Labor Force - NY Industries [cont.] (Box 44, Folder 39)
- Unemployment - Labor Force - NY Industries [cont.] (Box 44, Folder 40)
- Unemployment - Labor Force - NY Industries [cont.] (Box 44, Folder 41)
- U.I. Current (Box 44, Folder 42)
- U.I. Revisions - N.Y.S. (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Miscellaneous U.I. Material (Box 44, Folder 44)
- U.S. Medicine in Transition - Fortune, Dec. 1944 (Box 44, Folder 45)
- United States Senate Document No. 10, Admin. Procedure in Gov't. Agencies (Box 44, Folder 46)
- Unemployment Compensation: What and Why? (Box 44, Folder 47)
- Workmen's Compensation for Public Employees - Leifur Magnusson, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 48)
- NYS Dept. of Labor (Box 45, Folder 1)
- NYS Dept. of Labor (Box 45, Folder 2)
- NYS Unemployment (Box 45, Folder 3)
- General Motors Corp. - Unemployment (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Pension Plans / Unemployment Ins. (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Pension Plans / Unemployment Ins. [cont.] (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Interstate Conf. of Empl. Security Agencies (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Interstate Conf. of Empl. Security Agencies [cont.] (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Unemployment Benefits (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Unemployment Benefits [cont.] (Box 45, Folder 10)
- NYS Senate (Box 45, Folder 11)
- NYS Senate [cont.] (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Pension Agreements - Ithaca Industries (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Pension Planning for Dept. Stores (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Pension Plans - Michael Puchek (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Pension Plans (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Pensions: Misc. Reports (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Pensions - Misc. reports (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Private Pension Plans (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Private Pensions (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Problems of economic security (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Proposal - Study of Problems of Aging (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Question for Polls (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Railway Labor Dispute, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- NY Central, Penn. Merger - P.R. Program - Suppl. Mat'l. (Box 46, Folder 13)
- NY Central, Penn. Merger - P.R. Program - Suppl. Mat'l. [cont.] (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Railroad Social Security (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Congress of the United States (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Railway employees (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Railway employees [cont.] (Box 46, Folder 18)
- RLEA (Box 46, Folder 19)
- RLEA [cont.] (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Maritime Trades Dept. (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Seafarers International Union (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Railway Dispute - 1967: Responses by Congress and Affiliates of MTD, AFL-CIO (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Railway Disputes - Responses (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Railway Disputes - Responses (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Railway Disputes - Responses (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Railway Disputes - Responses (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Railway Disputes - Responses (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Railway Disputes - Responses (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Reprints - Problems of Method in Human Rel. (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Restrictive Legislation in Social Security (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Retirement Cases (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Retirement - Preparation for (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Retirement - Preparation for [cont.] (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Retirement Program - Amalgamated Clothing Workers (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Review of Problem of Unemployment Ins. Financing // Copy of Dean McConnell (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Annual Report: St. Louis Labor Health Inst. (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Social Security - Misc. Reports (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Social Security - Misc. Reports [cont.] (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Social Security Administration - Reports (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Social Security Administration - Reports [cont.] (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Social Security - Aid to the Blind, Children (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Social Security - Course Mat'l. (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Social Security - Food and Drug Regulation (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Social Security - Labor Problems - Social Economics - Employment and Remedies (Box 48, Folder 9)
- S.S. & Related Institutions in the U.S. (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Social Security System - Philippines (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Social Security in the United States (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Sociology (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Social Security - Misc. (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Misc. Mat'l. re SUB (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Misc. Mat'l. re SUB [cont.] (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Tennessee Valley Authority [cont.] (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Unemployment Insurance (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance [cont.] (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Unemployment Insurance Experience Rating (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Unemployment Insurance Experience Rating [cont.] (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Unemployment Insurance - Joint Leg. Committee Reports (Box 49, Folder 5)
- University Government Center - Social Security (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Utilization of Older Workers (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Veterans Benefits (Box 50, Folder 3)
- World in Which we Work (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Computer Output ILR 210 Survey // Clifton Taylor / ILR 210 / Nov. 8, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Computer Output ILR 210 Survey // Clifton Taylor / ILR 210 / Nov. 8, 1974 [cont.] (Box 50, Folder 6)
- JoAnn G. MacKenzie / ILR 210 / Computer Project / Part II: SPSS // Dec. 13, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- ILR 210 Term Project / F. Warren Ellish / Nov. 1974 // SPSS - Task A / SAS - Task B (Box 50, Folder 8)
- ILR 210 A Statistics / Mary Lou Serafini (Box 50.1, Folder 1)
- ILR 210 - Logbook/Crandall Clark (Box 50.1, Folder 2)
- Log Book - SAS & SPSS / Computer Task / Brian D. Dunn (Box 50.1, Folder 3)
- John Bramble / ILR 210 (Box 50.1, Folder 4)
- ILR 210 / Michael Bienthes (Box 50.1, Folder 5)
- ILR 210 / Kimball Smith SAS (Box 50.2, Folder 1)
- ILR 210 / Lori Segal SAS (Box 50.2, Folder 2)
- ILR 210 / Bette Wightman (Box 50.2, Folder 3)
- ILR 210 / Bette Wightman - TA - Susan Lynch (Box 50.2, Folder 4)
- ILR 210 / Susan Lynch SAS (Box 50.2, Folder 5)
- ILR 210 - Task B / Prof. Francis - Dec. 2, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- ILR 210 - Fred Staudmeyer (Box 51, Folder 2)
- ILR 210 - Mark Venuti (Box 51, Folder 3)
- ILR 210 - Brewster - SAS (Box 51, Folder 4)
- ILR 210 - Tom Darling/All runs prior to final/SPSS (Box 51, Folder 5)
- ILR 210 - Unlabeled printouts (Box 51, Folder 6)
- ILR 210 - Cynthia Shenker (Box 51.1, Folder 1)
- ILR 210 - Unlabeled Computer Printouts (Box 51.1, Folder 2)
- ILR 210 - Bruce Goldstein (Box 51.2, Folder 1)
- ILR 210 - Bruce Oitlin (Box 51.2, Folder 2)
- ILR 210 - John D. Mills (Box 51.2, Folder 3)
- ILR 210 - David Eisen (Box 51.2, Folder 4)
- ILR 210 - Bruce Gitlin (Box 51.2, Folder 5)
- ILR 210 - Howard Schochton (Box 52, Folder 1)
- ILR 210 - Howard Schochton (Box 52, Folder 2)
- ILR 210 - Lensky (Box 52, Folder 3)
- ILR 210 - Alan Green (Box 52, Folder 4)
- ILR 210 - Nora Burke (Box 52.1, Folder 1)
- ILR 210 - Nora Burke (Box 52.1, Folder 2)
- ILR 210 - Stephen Marsland (Box 52.1, Folder 3)
- ILR 210 - Robert Quintana (Box 52.1, Folder 4)
- ILR 210 - Diane Wood (Box 52.1, Folder 5)
- ILR 210 - Thomas Darling - Part B (Box 52.1, Folder 6)
- State of New York. Report of the Joint Legislation Committee on Unemployment Insurance, 1951-1952 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance / CIO (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Economic Security: Provisions in Private Industry, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Industrial Pensions and Retirement Procedures: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Key Facts as to the 1948-1956 Unemployment Fund Experience under the Law of Each State, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Report of the Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Legislative Recommendations of the Ohio State Advisory Council on Unemployment Compensation, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- State of NY, In Senate, No. 1851 (1957); Our Manpower Future-1955-65, 1955-1965 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- New York State Unemployment Insurance Law; Information for Employees on the NYS Unemployment; Compilation of the Social Security Laws, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Bureau of Employment Security; Unemployment Insurance; Comparison of State Unemployment Insurance Laws, 1953-1954 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Family Characteristics of the Long-Term Unemployed - Sept. 1962 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Family Characteristics of the Long-Term Unemployed - April 1962 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation Insurance and Pension Agreement, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Welfare Collective Bargaining In Action: A Case Study / Morris Sackman, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- ILR 470; Social Security Bulletin - Feb. 1947, 1947-1951 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Role of Lobbying in Representative Self-Government: part 1, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Information Cards - Netherlands; Denmark; Bolivia; Germany; Latin America; Norway; Uruguay; Eligibility; Administration (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Social Legislation and Work in Finland, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- German Experience with Social Insurance, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Why Social Security?; After the War - Toward Security; A.F. of L. wants F.E.P.C.; Educational aids available to community groups; An Equal Chance; Inside Facts; The Primer for the Public on the New Jersey; NYS Exec. Dept., Annual Report; State of Co, 1934-1948 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- John B. Andrews Memorial Symposium on Labor Legislation and Social Security, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- New York State Executive Dept. - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- New York State Exec. Dept. - Annual Rpt., 1947 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- New York State Executive Dept. - Annual Report 1946; New York State Commission Against Discrimination: A New Technique for an old problem (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Fortune - November 1949 / October 1949 (multiple copies of each) (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Collective Bargaining Provisions, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Union Health Center of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Lilly Retirement Plan, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Labor Management Conference on Working Together in a Democratic Society, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 28)
- Social Security: Past-Present-Future; Some Basic Readings in Social Security; Statement of Arthur J. Altmeyer, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Supplementation of Unemployment Benefits; An Analysis of the Ford Type Plan for Supplemental Unemployment Compensation; Secondary Labor Force and the Measurement of Unemployment, 1955-1957 (Box 53, Folder 30)
- United Automobile Worker (Oct. 1949); Reorganization Plan No. 2 of 1946; Reorganization Plan No. 1 of 1949; Office of Senator Hubert H. Humphrey (1949); United States Senate Memorandum; Enactment of a Law; Reducing Expenditures in Government; Elmir, 1946-1949 (Box 53, Folder 31)
- Sick-Pat Benefit Legislation: A Report; NYS Disability Benefits Law; Economic Report of the President; Council of Economic Advisers, 1948-1949 (Box 53, Folder 32)
- Wage Report; Trade Union as a wage fixing institution; Dynamics of wage determination under collective bargaining; Influence of unionism upon earnings (by Arthur M. Ross ); Productivity and the wage structure by John T. Dunlop; Basic criteria used in, 1945-1948 (Box 53, Folder 33)
- Survey of Income, Expenditures, and Savings Patterns; Glossary of currently-used wage terms; Wage and hour and public contracts div.; Critical analysis of sickness ins.; Studies in disability ins., 1934-1949 (Box 53, Folder 34)
- Charles Pearce Memo; Steel Labor no. 5, 7; Fortune Oct. & Nov. 1949, Pension Trust Statistical Tables, 1949-1951 (Box 53, Folder 35)
- Special Labor News Memo, no. 12; TVA Labor Relations; Causes of Industrial Peace Under Collective Bargaining; Perspectives of Elton Mayo; Profit sharing under collective bargaining; Health and efficiency of workers as affected by long hours and night, 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 36)
- Union and Union-Management Administered Health Insurance Plans in NYS; Welfare Funds in New York City Building Trades, 1950-1951 (Box 53, Folder 37)
- Social Security Legislation Throughout the World; Bibliographical Material on Foreign Labor Problems, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 38)
- Codified Summary of selected principles contained in the benefit decisions made by the umpire under the British Unemployment Insurance Acts, 1911- 1935 (Box 53, Folder 39)
- University of New Hampshire Commencement - Jan. 31, 1971 (program & photos) (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Social Insurance (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Economics of Labor Welfare Funds in the Coal Industries of the United States, Great Britain, and India: A Thesis (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Digest of Reports of the Consultants to the City of New York on its Retirement Systems, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- What we have learned from Working with the Poor by Eva Schindler-Rainman and Ronald Lippitt (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Health, Welfare and Pension Programs Under Wage Stabilization, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Manual of State Employment Security Legislation, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Health Costs of the Aged (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Pension Programming from a Labor Viewpoint (William Solenberger); Our program for social (George Meany); Grants to States for Old-Age Assistance (Box 54, Folder 10)